ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Clergy, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Clergy, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- City/State Purchasing, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Contributions, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- JPS. Black Clergy, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Press Clipping Service. Burrelle's, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- CLUW. JPS., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Conventions, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Designers: Pleshette, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Designers: Dinah Shore, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Demonstrations. An Open Letter to the New York Board of Trade, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Designers: Others, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Disclosure, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- JPS Display, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Donations, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Entertainment, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- ESOP, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- JPS. EEOC Model Cases, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- JPS. EEOC, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Educational Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Fan/Crank Mail, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Fact Sheet, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Fact Sheet (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Premiere. "Testimony", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Premiere "Testimony" Lists, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Testimony Film: Justice vs. J. P. Stevens, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- ACTWU Film, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Film (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Leaflets and Literature, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Literature, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Leaflets, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Samples of Literature and Leaflets, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Literature and Leaflets [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Literature and Leaflets [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Literature and Leaflets [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Literature and Leaflets [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- National Women's Committee (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Social Justice. No.1-25, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Missing No. 2 and 24.
- Social Justice. No.1-25., 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Missing No. 2, 9, and 26. Copy 2.
- Social Justice. No. 1-25., 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Missing No. 2, 9, 15, 17, and 24. Copy 3.
- Social Justice Index. No.27-31., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Missing No.30.
- Boycott (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Spanish Boycott (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Correspondence. Justice for JPS Workers Day. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  November 30th
- Correspondence. Justice for JPS Workers Day. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Correspondence. Justice for JPS Workers Day., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- JPS Workers Day. Demo, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- JPS Workers Day. Demo, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Ads: JPS. Gimbels., 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Talking Points on JPS. Memoranda., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Staff Mailings, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Staff Mailings. Social Justice. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Staff Mailings. Social Justice. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Staff Mailings, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Staff Mailings, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Staff Mailings, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Staff Mailings., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Staff Mailings. [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Staff Mailings., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Virginia
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Montgomery, Alabama
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Little Rock
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Hollywood,CA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Boston, Mass
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Los Angeles, CA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Delaware
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Tifton, GA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Atlanta, GA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  May 19th. Chicago.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Baltimore, MD
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Detroit, Mich.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Minneapolis, MN.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  St. Paul, MN.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  St. Louis, MO.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  New York
- JPS. Tax Evasion/Avoidance, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- J. P. S. Documents, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- J. P. S., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- J. P. S., 1970-1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- From Family Firm to Corporate Giant. Responses to Points Made in Heritage Foundation Report., 1813-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- J. P. S., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- J. P. S. Misc. [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- J. P. S. Misc. [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Seattle, Wash.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Washington, D.C.
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Knoxville, TN
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Cleveland
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Pittsburgh, PA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Philadelphia, PA
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Cincinnati, OH
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Winston. Salem, NC
- Crystal Lee (Norma Rae), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Roanoke Rapids, NC
- Macy's Davisons, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Georgia
- Macy's. [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Macy's. [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- National Retail Chain Mailings, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Block's, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Donaldson's Allied, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Jordan Marsh, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Levy's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Savannah
- Troutman's Allied, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Roninson's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Florida
- AYERS, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Stix, Baer and Fuller, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Federated, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Federated, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Federated (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Abraham and Straus [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Abraham and Straus [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Bloomingdale's, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Allied, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Gold Circle, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Bullock's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Lazarus, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Filene's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Federated Reports, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Rike's Federated, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Shillito's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Macy's, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Macy's, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Macy's Bamburger's, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Macy's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  California
- Letters to Lazarus, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Rich's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Big K. Kuhn's, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Macy's Corporate, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- May Co. Corporate, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- May Co., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  Ohio
- May Co. Meier and Frank, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- May Co. Hect Co., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- May Co., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Strouss, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Akron, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  Southern California
- Altman's, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Bradlee's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  Stop and Start
- Broadway (Carter, Hawley, Hale), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Chappell's, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Clarkin Unistops, Inc, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- May D and F, The Denver, Joslin's, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Denver
- The Diamond (Associated), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- G. C. Murphy, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- GeeBee, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Mercantile, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Hill (SCOA), 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Howland Steinbach, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Supermarkets General Corp.
- Kervettes, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Mervyn's Dayton Hudson, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- J. C. Penny, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Strawbridge and Clothier, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- K-Mart, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- G. C. Murphy's, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Sears, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- House of Fabrics, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- L. S. Good and Co., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Gimbels, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Gimbels, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Montgomery Ward, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Woolworth and Wolcott [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Woolworth and Wolcott [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Woolward and Lothrop, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Zakre's [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Zakre's [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Status Reports, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Status Reports, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Status Reports, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Status Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Status Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Status Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Status Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Sit. Report, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Field Activity. Local Campaigns. Federated, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Materials Accompanying Status Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Materials Accompanying Status Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- A. D. Magazine, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- AVON, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- C-LIST. Voluntary Actions By Retailers., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- City/State Hearings, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Campus Support, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- C. L. U. W., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Corporate Campaign, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Cups. Boycott (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Disclosure, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Hotel Program [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Hotel Program [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens Notes [folder 1 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens Notes [folder 2 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens Notes [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Legal [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Legal [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Manufacturers Hanover Trust. [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Manufacturers Hanover Trust. [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- National Endorsements, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- J. P. Stevens. Financial Campaign, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Millegdeville. Summary of Deposition/Affidavits., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- New York Life, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Norma Rae. [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Norma Rae. [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Reaction to J. P. Stevens, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- November 30th [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- November 30th [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Originals, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Phoning, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Press. Coded, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- PX, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Religious Constituency [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Religious Constituency [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Religious Constituency, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Religious Endorsements, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Seaman's Bank, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Surveys, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  September 1979
- Surveys, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  September 1977
- Staff Benefits, 1946-1974 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Staff Meetings, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Staff Meeting, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  April 9-11th. Philadelphia, PA
- Staff Weekly Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Stockholders Meeting, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  January (Only)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  December (Only)
- Stockholders Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  December
- Stockholders Meeting, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  January to November
- T-Shirts, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- United Presbyterian U. S.A, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  General Assembly
- West Coast, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  June
- Wm. Somplatsky-Jarman's Report to UpUSA Church, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Macy's Co. Letter (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Macy's Report Forms (Box 20, Folder 2)
  blank forms
- Field Staff. Sperry Campaign. Stevens again guilty violating law., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Field Staff, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Re: Southern Bishops
- DNR. Articles. Originals, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Other Originals, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Macy's Store Survey Forms, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Macy's Reports, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Macy's, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Macy's, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Retail Store Survey Forms (Box 20, Folder 11)
- RN Numbers (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Weekly Activity Report Forms (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Woolworth Surveys [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Woolworth Surveys [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Woolworth /W. target stores, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Woolworth [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Woolworth [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Woolworth/Woolco Store Visits, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Abraham and Straus Store Surveys, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  originals
- Zayre's Reports, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Tony DuCharme, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Mike Schippani, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- William McKersie, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Carol Colbeth, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- George Grabianowski, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Margaret Banks [folder 1 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Margaret Banks [folder 2 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Margaret Banks [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Michael Blaine, 1973-1977 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Frank Red Byers. J. P. Stevens, 1973-1977 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Henry Carter. J. P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- James Cleary [folder 1 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- James Cleary [folder 2 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- James Cleary [folder 3 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- James Cleary [folder 4 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- James Cleary [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- James Cleary [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Shanon Farrell, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Richard Flando, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Paul Horowitz, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Frieda Jones, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Michael Matusick, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Joseph Mello. J. P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Linda Paguette. J. P. Stevens, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Emilio Molleda, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Richard Moore, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Alice Senturia, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Maureen Ferrin, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- NYC Committee for Justice, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens Misc. Documents, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Senior Thesis. "ACTWU vs. JPS. A Case Study of an Effort to Unionize Southern Textile Workers", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  pages 1-77
- Senior Thesis. "ACTWU vs. JPS. A Case Study of an Effort to Unionize Southern Textile Workers", 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  pages 78-155/end.
- Southern Exposure. Building South., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  v.8:no.1 (1980:Spring)
- Southern Exposure. Here Come a Wind., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  v.4:no.1/2 (1976:Spring/Summer)
- Abraham and Straus Store Survey Form, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Letterhead Bond Paper (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Envelopes (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Mailings sent out, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Mailings Sent Out, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  Copies
- Mailings. Resolution. Blank Resolution Forms., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Business Cards, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Staff Misc., 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Staff Lists (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Artha Adair, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Ed Allen, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Jim Anderson, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Jim Anderson, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Sarah Broom, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  photograph included
- Steven Burrell, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Bob Bussel, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Bob Bussel, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Bill Callahan, 1978-1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Brant Carleton, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Gene Carroll, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Stan Clair, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Carol Colbeth, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Tony DuCharme, 1978-1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- David Dyson, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Larry Frank, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Joel Gay, 1976-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Hy Goldberg, 1976-1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Hy Goldberg, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Pete Goldstein, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- George Grabianowski, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Leon Hall, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Sam Hirsch, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Ronald Hooks, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Jerry Landman, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Michael Paul Linfield, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Jeannie Maynard, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- John MC Donough, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Bill McKersie, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Barbara Merrill, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Paul Mignini, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Paul Mignini, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Paul Minkoff, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Dolores J. Moss, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Erika M. Outland, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Katherine Papa [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Katherine Papa [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Bill Patterson, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Joseph Pilati, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Teresa S. Rankin, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Mike Schippani, 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Ray Rogers, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- John Rizzo, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- May Smith, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Mae Smith, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Carol Somplatsky-Jarman, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- William Somplatsky-Jarman [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- William Somplatsky-Jarman [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Dan Starnes, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Julia Stewart, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Roberta Stovitz, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Mike Szpak [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Mike Szpak [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Father Patrick Sullivan, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- William Somplatsky- Jarman, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Michael Szpak, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Harriet Teller Goldman, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  card with photograph included
- Frank Vardeman-Hilf, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Pam Woywod, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Media Coverage for Crystal Lee Sutton, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Carmela Speranza, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Pam Woywod Letters, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Gail Jeffords, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Martha Wilson, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Mary Ann Ciro, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Patricia Cunningham, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Dayton, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Eneida Garcia, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Gregory Hamaty, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Susan Kessel, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Vicki King, 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Crystal Lee Sutton, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Crystal Lee Sutton, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Crystal Lee Sutton, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Crystal Lee Sutton. General- Financial and Legal, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Crystal Lee Sutton Tour, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Crystal Lee Sutton responses, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Crystal Lee Sutton, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Tony DuCharme. Bookmark, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Letters. Supporters, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Artha Adair, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Jim Anderson, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Robert Bussel, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Sarah Broom, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Steve Burrell, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Joel Gay, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Hy Goldberg, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Pete Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- San Hirsch, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Ronald Hooks, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Michael Linfield [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Michael Linfield [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- John McDonough, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Barbara Merrill [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Michael Linfield [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Paul Mignini, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Erika Outland, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Katherine Papa, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Bill Patterson, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Stan Clair, 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Teresa Rankin, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- John Rizzo, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Buster Smith, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Mae Smith, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Mike Szpaz, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Martha Wilson, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Legal Models [folder 1 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Legal Models [folder 2 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Legal Models [folder 3 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Legal Models [folder 4 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Memos to General Officers [folder 1 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Memos to General Officers [folder 2 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Memos to General Officers [folder 3 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- ACTWU. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- ACTWU. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Memos to General Officers [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Memos to General Officers [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Memos to Finance, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Memos to Department Heads, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Memos to Legal, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Memos to Del Mileski, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Memos to others, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Memos to Burt Beck [folder 1 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Memos to Burt Beck [folder 2 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Memos to Burt Beck [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Memos to Pilat/Herriman. Harry Wittschen [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Memos to Pilat/Herriman. Harry Wittschen [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Memos to HDS, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Cancellations, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Rally, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Retail Letter (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Brunch Meeting (Box 26, Folder 11)
- NYC Citizens, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Pamphlets, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  2 sheets of photographs included
- Stevens Campaign Songs, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)